Who fired that arrow?
Could there be others who want Zhu Huaichen dead?
Perhaps he can be of use to me
Who's there?
My lord, is that you?
Catch the assassin!
I remember this guy being sickly
Could he have been faking it all along?
Hiding his martial arts skills to kill Zhu Huaichen?
That consumptive wretch
People are born with different constitutions
Not to mention different life experiences
Given the choice
Everyone would prefer health and safety
Don't you agree, Third Prince?
Catch the assassin!
Search every single one of them
Search them all! Yes sir!
Well?
Nothing, nothing found
Why are you wearing wedding attire?
How dare you!
You scoundrel! How could you...
My apologies
That madwoman dared to blind me
I'll have her executed immediately
Don't be angry, Chen Lang
Killing her now
would be letting her off too easy
We haven't settled the score from the martial arts tournament yet
She made you lose face
before His Majesty and all the princes
We should keep her alive
and torture her slowly
Besides, we still need her to find the Dragon Jade
Death would be too merciful for her
I want her to wish she were dead
Exactly, Chen Lang
And as you've said before, Chen Lang
Li Zhi'an and the old Li family troops haven't surrendered yet
If we can gain control of their former military forces
It will greatly aid your ambitious conquest
The dragon jade contains a treasure map left by the Li family ancestors
Rumored to rival all the wealth in the world
Only by obtaining the dragon jade treasure
Can one truly unify the realm
It seems they're searching for the dragon jade
Third Prince
Have you found it?
Reporting Your Highness, nothing in the house
Dismissed
Yes
Huaichen, is that you?
Zhi'an
It's me
Yesterday I accidentally injured my husband
How are your injuries now?
I'm perfectly fine
No need to worry
Attendants!
The princess consort has awakened
Prepare to depart once ready
Husband, you're hurting me
You must be angry with me, aren't you?
Not at all
By the way, Zhian, it's a long journey ahead
The important item your father-in-law gave you
Make sure to keep it safe
You have eye problems
If it's inconvenient
You can entrust it to me
Trying to trick me into handing over the Dragon Jade
Too bad you don't even know what Dragon Jade is
If that bitch hadn't betrayed me in my past life
Even I wouldn't have known about it
Important things
I just remembered
Father once said
His most precious possession was me
Now that I'm your wife
As long as you protect me well
Won't you be holding the most important treasure?
You
Imperial Brother
The Li family army has come to see off Your Highness and Lady Li
Let's not keep them waiting
I will never let you have your way
We've searched the entire general's residence
But found no trace of the Dragon Jade
Useless fools
Get out
Yes
Imperial Brother, news has spread about how the Northern Jin royal family slaughtered General Li's entire household
Taking advantage of the drunken wedding banquet
In their attempt to seize the Dragon Jade
Now all the former northern division generals are waiting outside
They demand to witness Li Zhi'an's departure from Northern Jin with their own eyes
These old Li family loyalists are hard to deceive
Imperial Brother can tolerate their insolence for a few more days
Once we reach Nanliang territory
After gaining the trust of those troops
We'll eliminate those generals one by one
Then we won't have to worry about these forces not submitting to you
Is this plan of yours reliable?
I've already played the pitiful orphan
too fragile to endure more suffering
persuaded the generals to conceal the massacre of the Li family
from Miss Li
Moreover, the Emperor lost an eye for Miss Li's sake
They certainly won't suspect anything now
Zhi'an
Your parents couldn't bear the separation
so I didn't let them come to see us off
Huai Chen
Let me bow here to bid farewell to my parents
Now the only way is to produce the Li family's military token
to alert the uncles that something's wrong
and stop me from leaving the mansion
But Zhu Huaichen might have anticipated this
Today marks the young mistress's wedding
We, the remaining Li family troops, respectfully send off our young mistress
As expected, we can't use the secret token to warn the Li army
Ambushes are everywhere
Respected uncles
You've watched Zhi'an grow up
and now you're escorting her to her wedding
One day
Zhi'an will repay your kindness
Now my Li family has been falsely accused of treason
Only by going to Nanliang to expose Zhu Huaichen's conspiracy
can I clear my name and take revenge